<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VLCC Institute</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="about_vlcc_gzb">Looking for an institute which specialises in Nutrition,Dietician , Makeup, Hair ,skin and many other  courses? why go anywhere else when VLCC Institute of Vaishali ,Ghaziabad gets to you the best of the offers and education. VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad offers you to choose from 50+ courses available. Study and practice for just a couple of months and get a job which fetches you minimum of Rs15,000 .Having successfully trained and placed more than 100,000 candidates so far,VLCC Institute Alumni are working in every nook and corner of the country. So, placements at VLCC institute of Ghaziabad need not to be worried upon. VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad ensures 100% placement opportunities for students. VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad believes in providing students with opportunities to learn from the real world experience, even during their student life. VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad understands your needs and hence offers a "flexible learning" programme where students may attend classes part time, full time ,weekend or interval bases. Courses of VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad are approved by IAO. Not willing to pay now or having financial instabilities? No worries! VLCC Institute of Ghaziabad follows a friendly loan system wherein one may do the course without paying a single rupee and without any conditions of guarantee or securities.So what are you waiting for? apply and register Now.</string>
    <string name="about_us">To ensure a better quality of life for everyone, by adopting and pursuing ethically and socially relevant business practices aimed at shaping up people’s confidence and making Slimming, Beauty and Health accessible to all sections of our society.</string>
    <string name="founder_msg">I tried, to bring back the hope in weary eyes, beauty in cynical faces, and a glow in jaded halos. It was almost a decade ago that I treaded on the delicate terrain of others’ dreams. I tried, in my own little way to usher in the mantra of ‘look good, feel great’. Nothing gave me a bigger high than to see the glow on a patron’s face who, a couple of months ago came to me dejected, dismayed and with zero confidence. My dedicated team went to task, re-sculpted the persona and today the same life has an attitude and is all set to go out, be with friends, experiment with life, wear clothes that accentuate the body beautiful and face life with a whole new energy. A new karma. And it is with wings set to fly that I have set up this institution. The idea is to see the same glow, the same positivity.
I welcome you to VLCC Institute of Beauty and Nutrition with a humble hope that we can once again bring back smiles as we have done in the past with other VLCC endeavors.</string>
    <string name="introduction">VLCC Institute of Beauty and Nutrition was established in India in 2001 to share VLCC’s dream with today’s students and tomorrow’s entrepreneurs. Headquartered in Gurgaon. The Institutes offer specialized professional courses in beauty, hair, cosmetology, make-up, spa therapies and nutrition.</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="makeup1">Makeup Theory, Tools of Makeup, Different Eye Makeup, Day Makeup (3 types), Evening Makeup, Engagement Makeup, Reception Makeup, Bridal Makeup, Groom Makeup, Corrective Makeup, Ramp Makeup, Illusion Makeup (Old Age Look, Cut and Burn Marks, Beard Look, Accident Mark), Portfolio Makeup, Fantasy Makeup (Face Art), Glossy Makeup, Tan Makeup. Indian Bride In Seven Looks, Blemished Skin Makeup, Tan Makeup, Yellow Makeup, Glamour Makeup, Page 3 Makeup, High definition Makeup, Airbrush Body Makeup with silicone Base, Casualty Simulation, 3D prosthetics and Special Effect Makeup.</string>
    <string name="makeup2">Personal Hygiene, Pre-Bridal Consultancy, CTM for Birdal, Color Theory, Color Correction of The Complexion, Shading and Contouring, Step-By-Step Application, Bridal Tips, Dierent Bridal Makeup, 5 Hair Styles for 5 Different Brides.</string>
    <string name="hair_opp">On the successful completion of course in Hair Technology qualified candidates can work as a Hair Stylist, Freelancer, Faculty, Technical Trainer, Media House, Salon owner</string>
    <string name="makeup_opp">On the successful completion of course in Makeup Artist, Fashion Makeup Artist, Media Artist, Makeup Consultant, Makeup Trainer, Color Cosmetic Advisor, Freelancer</string>
    <string name="nutrition_opp">On the successful completion of course in Nutrition, qualified candidate can work in Hospitals, Nursing Homes, Corporate Houses, Slimming Centers, Gym, Hotels</string>
    <string name="cosmetology_opp">On the successful completion of course in Aesthetics, qualified candidates are assisted for placement to work as Laser Aesthetician under Dermatologists or in Medispa or Laser Clinics.</string>
</resources>
